https://www.texlawyers.com/privacy-policy

FREE CASE REVIEWNO FEE UNLESS YOU COLLECT (817) 531-3000 HELP AVAILABLE 24/7 info@texlawyers.com
We are committed to serving you without contact while we all remain safe from COVID-19. [LEARN MORE]$4.3 MILLIONRecovery to ClientTruck Injury Partial Paralysis$3.4 MILLIONRecovery to ClientsTruck Collision Injuries to Spine, Brain, Spleen, Forearm$7.1 MILLIONRecovery to ClientTruck Accident - Injury$847 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientCar Accident Injury to Abdomen & Neck$3.6 MILLIONRecovery to ClientSailboat Accident Electrical Shock$9.1 MILLIONRecovery to ClientMedical Injury Brain Damage$2.2 MILLIONRecovery to ClientTruck Injury Paralysis$2.3 MILLIONRecovery to ClientManufacturer Defect Fatality$933 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientTruck Injury Paralysis$7.5 MILLIONRecovery to ClientMedical Injury Brain Damage$1.2 MILLIONRecovery to ClientGarbage Truck Collision Fatality$827 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientDUI Collision Wife: Neck/Shoulder Injury, Husband: Fatality$1.3 MILLIONRecovery to ClientTrucking Collision Fatality$8.7 MILLIONRecovery to ClientMedical Injury Brain Damage$750 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientTrucking Collision Fatality$1.7 MILLIONRecovery to ClientTrucking Collision Injury Brain Damage$742 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientVan Collision Injury Brain Damage$7.2 MILLIONRecovery to ClientMedical Injury Brain Damage$604 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientDrunk Driving Accident Fatality$632 THOUSANDRecovery to ClientCommercial Truck Collision Fatality
Home » Privacy PolicyOur Privacy PoliciesThis privacy policy sets out how The Law Offices of Steven C. Laird, P.C. uses and protects any information that you give The Law Offices of Steven C. Laird, P.C when you use this website. The Law Offices of Steven C. Laird, P.C is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.The Law Offices of Steven C. Laird, P.C may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Changes will be noted on this page. This policy is effective from January 1, 2014.WHAT WE COLLECTWe may collect the following information:Name and job titleContact information including email addressDemographic information such as IP address, preferences and interestsOther information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHERWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.SECURITYWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.HOW WE USE COOKIESA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze Web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better Website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You may choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESOur website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@texlawyers.com. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.Legal Rights VideosWhy Steven Laird Steve Laird is among a distinguished and exclusive number of lawyers in Texas who are board certified in three specific areas of practice.View Steve Laird's ProfileNews & UpdatesLaw Firm News And UpdatesNews And Updates From The Fort Worth Law Firm Of Steven C. Laird, P.C.Over the years, attorneys at the Law Offices of Steven C. Laird have become trusted... Read more...Free Case Review (817)531-3000 HELP 24/7 HomeAbout UsSteven C. LairdSeth McCloskeyTypes of CasesPersonal InjuryWrongful DeathTrucking AccidentsCar WrecksConstruction AccidentsDefective ProductsOil and Gas Field InjuriesCase ResultsTestimonialsNews & Media CoverageLegal Articles & PresentationsAccident Information & HelpLegal Bloglegal insightstruck accidentcar wreckcrane accidentscorporate negligenceinsurance industry tacticsjurymedical malpracticeoilfield injuriespersonal injuryproduct liabilityvictims rightsContact
